cashnads.biz 2009-03-12

# CashnAds

### Privacy Policy

## AMENDED: March 6, 2009

Thank you for visiting CashnAds.Biz We appreciate the opportunity to interact with you on the Internet and are committed to protecting and safeguarding your privacy. The purpose of this Privacy Statement is to inform you about the types of information we might collect about you when you visit our Site, how we may use that information and whether we disclose that information to anyone. 

Any information we collect on our Site generally falls into the Personally Identifiable Information category. This refers to information that lets us know specifically who you are. In general, you can visit our Site without telling us who you are or revealing any Personally Identifiable Information. 

When you place an order for products or services, we collect Personally Identifiable Information (such as name, contact and billing information, email, and other transaction information). We use this information to deliver your order, process payment, and to communicate with you about the status of your order. Credit card information submitted with your order is used only for payment processing through third party payment processing and is not retained on our Site. 

Except as disclosed in this Privacy Statement, we do not sell, trade, rent, or otherwise retransmit any Personally Identifiable Information we collect online unless we have your permission. Any Personally Identifiable Information you provide to us will be used for your purchases and retained in hard copy form of the original invoice as well as within our database system. 

From time to time, we may be required to provide Personally Identifiable Information in response to court order, subpoena, or government investigation. We also reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful. We may release Personally Identifiable Information when we believe that such release is reasonably necessary to enforce or apply our Limited Warranty or to protect the rights, property, and safety of others and ourselves. 

CashnAds.Biz contains links to third-party Web sites which may be provided solely for your information and convenience, or to provide additional information for various other goods and services. If you use these links, you will leave our Site. This Privacy Statement does not cover the information practices of those Web sites linked to our Site, nor do we control their content or privacy policies. We suggest that you carefully review the privacy policies of each site you visit. 

Any updates or changes to the terms of this Privacy Statement will be posted here on our Site and the date of the newest version posted below. Please check back frequently, especially before you submit any Personally Identifiable Information at our Site, to see if this Privacy Statement has changed. By using our Site, you acknowledge acceptance of this Privacy Statement in effect at the time of use. If you have any concerns about our use of your information or about this Privacy Statement, please send an e-mail to CashnAds.Biz 

1\. **COOKIES**  
1.1. Your browser must accept cookies so we can store information.

1.2. Cookies will only be used to store your preferences and no identifiable information.

2\. **USER EMAILS**  
2.1. We will not share, sell, or trade your information.

2.2. We may use your email to contact you at any time.

2.3. We will use your payment accounts to pay you.

3\. **USER PASSWORD**  
3.1. Your password is saved safely in our database through undecryptable 256-bit binary encryption.

4\. **USERNAME**  
4.1. Your username will be shown, and may be shown by us at anytime.

4.2. Your username will show in the chat and forum.

5\. **ADVERTISEMENTS**  
5.1. We try to avoid offensive ads. If one is displayed, please report it at contact@cashnads.biz and we will remove it.

5.2. If you click an ad, you are expected to view it.

5.3. You must obey the rules of websites you visit while using our service.
